

Cristiano Louriceira Martins

🔁 cristianomartins96@hotmail.com 📞 +351.911834635 👂 Amiais de Baixo, Portugal 😝 B/B1

Profile

Academically, I have a degree in "Geography and Regional Planning", Master in "Territory Management with specialization in Remote Sensing and Geographic Information Systems" as well as two non-curricular internships in the area. Professionally, I work as a simplified registration technician (BUPi).

Finally, without any academic or professional commitment, I still have a website that I maintain as a hobby:

https://cristianolm.github.io/presentation/ ☑

Professional Experience

Simplified registry technician (Bupi),

07/2023 - present

Socarto - Sociedade De Levantamentos Topo Cartográficos, Lda. 🛭 Mapping of rustic and mixed properties in a GIS environment.

Temporary collaboration, *The USE Concept, Lda.*

12/2019 - 03/2020

Update of characterization and diagnostic studies, for review of the PDM of Caldas da Rainha.

Lisbon, Portugal

Internship, The USE Concept, Lda.

Review of PDM's and topographic cartography update.

02/2019 - 08/2019 Lisbon, Portugal

- Conversion of CAD data to GIS in order to build a database, to be used in the production of base cartography;
- · Support to report writing;
- Data acquisition;
- Cartographic editing;
- Quality control;
- Field completion.

Internship, CICS.NOVA

07/2017 - 08/2017

Internship in Interdisciplinary Center for Social Sciences at the NOVA University of Lisbon and two publications.

Lisbon, Portugal

Publication links 🛮

Sporadic jobs 2012 - present

- Auto Painter Helper (Amiais de Baixo (Portugal))
- Factory worker (Indutan // Comércio e Indústria de Peles, S.A.., Amiais de Cima (Portugal);
- Strawberry plantation (Herdade da Fragaria, Amiais de Baixo (Portugal));
- Grape picking (Malaqueijo (Portugal));

· Pear picking;

Education

Master in Territory Management with specialization in Remote Sensing and Geographic Information Systems,

10/2019 – 03/2021 Lisbon, Portugal

Faculty of Social and Human Sciences at NOVA University of Lisbon

Master thesis г₹

Minor in International Relations,

03/2018 - 06/2018

Faculty of Social and Human Sciences at NOVA University of Lisbon

Graduation in Geography and Regional Planning,

10/2015 - 06/2018

Faculty of Social and Human Sciences at NOVA University of Lisbon

Lisbon, Portugal

Skills

Microsoft Office

Word - Excel - PowerPoint

GIS Software

ArcMap - eCognition - QGIS

Version Control System

GIT

Web programming

HTML - CSS - JavaScript/TypeScript - React - GIT/Github

- MariaDB/MySQL.

Courses

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Udemy ♂

The Complete Quality Assurance Course-Learn QA from Scratch, Udemy ☑

Javascript Tutorial and Projects Course (2022), Udemy 🗷

The Git & Github Bootcamp, Udemy □

The Ultimate MySQL Bootcamp: Go from SQL Beginner to Expert, Udemy ☑

The Linux Command Line Bootcamp: Beginner To Power User, Udemy ☑

Programador Web Full-Stack, *Codemaster* □

Canguages

• Portuguese

English